flameupload.com 2010-12-31

# FlameUpload | Upload Everywhere!

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.   
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
� To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature   
� To send periodic emails 

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.   
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

**How do we protect your information?**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.   
This policy was last modified on 01/01/2009 

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
flameupload@gmail.com 

A free online file upload distribution service..to help you keep your shared files using several different web hosting providers. 

Providing free file uploads with one click to upload files to many hosts for files upto 200 MB. 

Suitable for your music, videos, movies, images or documents.
